## **Emmanuel Owolabi**

## Frontend Developer

Striving self-taught frontend developer offering 1 year of experience in providing skills in the areas of decision making, communication, evaluation and team work in frontend web solutions. Looking forward to being proficient in designing, developing and testing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Also aspiring to combine broad background with strong technical skills, practices and procedures to bring significant improvements in efficiency, productivity and business processes as a Front-End Developer.



# Work History

#### **Address**

Ojodu-Berger, Lagos, 100234

#### **Phone**

+2348138469203

#### E-mail

owoemma59@gmail.com

#### **Twitter**

www.twitter.com/infiniti0x

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/emmanuel-owolabi-6b5b7



HTML5

Excellent

BOOTSTRAP

CSS3

Very Good

VANILLA

JAVASCRIPT

Very Good

REACT

Very Good

### 2021-11 -Current

## **Front End Developer**

Inzira Tech (self-employed), Ojodu-Berger, Lagos

- Use regulatory and compliance standards for user interface designs.
- Contributed to projects within Scrum project management environments.
- Created mobile applications based on React, integrating Facebook's best practices for interface design.
- Maintained high-level expertise in React state management strategies.
- Developed clear specifications for project plans using customer requirements.

### 2019-04 -2019-09

## **Civil Engineering Intern**

Centre Base Consult LTD, Ikeja, Lagos

- Accompanied senior technical staff for on-site inspections during construction, learning how to communicate design requirements with contractors and equipment suppliers.
- Assisted project engineers with phases of civil and site development, including grading and roadway design, storm water management system design and erosion and sediment control design.
- Collected and entered data, and applied technical principles and theories to assist in

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP



interpreting and analyzing data.



English ••••

Very Good

Yoruba ••••

Excellent

**Education** 

2015-11 - Bachelor Of Engineering: Civil

<sup>2021-03</sup> Engineering

Olabisi Onabanjo University - Ogun State

2021-05 - Kotlin For Android

2021-12 Android Developers - Developers.android.com